[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "But what are you trying to achieve with the cable news genre, if anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I -- I'm only trying to achieve one thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "When you said it, did you believe it yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "It was interesting to do the speech, to work on the speech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "If it's -- now you've had your toes dipped in our waters for a while, if you were running a news network, what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, first, let me just backup a little bit and say I don't have to live in the real world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Are Americans still the hardest working people on earth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "You didn't write the speech though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "But I mean for a president to be standing there today deliberately pandering like that to the Latino community at a Latino conference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Am I being too cynical here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "No, no, of course you're not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "But what -- why do you like that solitude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well, I liked it then because of the drug use.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Have you arrived at a good place in your life now, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "The hard way, maybe, but you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I'm the luckiest guy in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Every so often, I'm a single man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["million dollars"]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "How much money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "A million dollars a year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "You get back $1 million a year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["Three million dollars"]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "You paid $1 million to be able to fire me anytime you want?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Three million dollars.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "A great role, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What's Emily Mortimer like to work with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "She's a dream.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Emily Mortimer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Well, they've clearly had a fling before, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Keith Olbermann"]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "-- mad as hell?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "-- base it on Keith Olbermann, I missed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "To which the answer was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Spencer Tracy"]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Yes, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I actually think he's the new Spencer Tracy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What is the art of great acting, other than listening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Listening is a bit part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "And, Jeff, when you look around now in the firmament of great actors, who, for you, stands out, male or female, right now as pound for pound a great actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "You know, Meryl.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim Carey"]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "What have you heard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "That Jim Carey buggered off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Starting to do well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yeah, starting to creep back to where it was before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["10:00 p.m."]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "10:00 p.m.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Am I allowed to call you Todd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "You should -- you're definitely allowed to call me Todd.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "When you heard what has happened, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, you know, my first reaction was -- it was horrifying, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Did you know Whitney well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes, I knew Whitney.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What gave you that idea to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "You know, I -- I was thinking about it and it was the only way that I felt -- I would feel comfortable proceeding with the show and celebrating all of these other musicians, because it was about trying to find that fine balance between celebrating her legacy, giving love to this wonderful, amazing entertainer, and, at the same time, respecting all of these young artists and all of these established artists who were either nominated for Grammys or performing on the show and not putting them in the position where they have to perform at a memorial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Do you understand the particular pressure, as a former -- that led her to enter that spiral of self-abuse towards the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "JJ", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Of course I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Was music always your first love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Well -- well, yes, you drift away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBG", "PRP"], "qSentId": 762, "question": "What is it to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "Whatever goal I'm going -- I want to achieve, achieving it", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "Oh, God, I don't even want to think about that, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "I'm not saying it's going to happen imminently.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "But, you know, things -- all being relative and everything being even, it's what you don't do that you'll ultimately regret, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ":", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "Well, you're doing a hell of a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "My Connect Studio is available now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "When is the new album out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "You know what, I'm working on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "Will you please, please marry me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]